

Osman BOLAT Industrial Engineering

ABOUT

By combining the knowledge, I gained during the university period with the experience I gained in the companies I worked for, I aim to work on innovative and continuous progress within a well-established and large company like yours. I plan to carry out studies that will increase the quality of the company by working with a focus on customers and quality. As a result of giving me a chance, I aim to gain a permanent place in your company by achieving controlled development with your company, which is the Pioneer and follower of technological and strategic developments in the sector.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

TUPRAS(KIRIKKALE)

Planning Engineer (Intern) (July 2023 - July 2023)

 I learned the process of obtaining the required amount of white product with the desired properties by processing the crude oil in different units. I learned that some of the tanks are sales tanks, and some are spare tanks, how to follow the occupancy rate of the tanks containing the ready-to-sale product, and how to prepare for sale.

DORA MAKINA(ANKARA)

Planning Engineer (Candidate Engineer) (June 2021 - September 2021)

 Aselsan, Roketsan, TAI etc. in the CANIAS program, I learned to follow the factory production of the parts requested by the business partner companies and to control the ERP and MRP systems. I learned about the process of Quality Control, Production planning, Quality Process Management, Weld Inspection, Levelling and Production, and Milling and Turning units.

Mercedes-Benz Aydoğanlar Otomotiv (ANKARA)

Service Consultant (İntern) (July 2017- August 2017)

 To follow up the maintenance and repair processes required for vehicles.

Mossback Restaurant (OHIO/USA)

Kitchen Helper (June 2022- September 2022)

 I have been on the island of Put in bay, OHİO, USA for 5 months with the Work and Travel program. I had the opportunity to meet people from different cultures and improve my English there.

LC WAİKİKİ(ANKARA)

Cashier assistant manager (November 2016- May 2022)

PROJECT AND SEMINARS

2017: Electric Bike

2022: HACETTEPE Career Fair

2022: Production Process Optimization

2023: Refinery Model Optimization

CONTACT AND PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of birth : 17.01.1997

Adress : İstasyon Mah. Polatlı 1 caddesi sakin

yuva konutları 33/19 Sincan/ANKARA

Driver License: Class B **Phone Number** 0 543 566 2073

E-Posta : bolatosman 66@hotmail.com
LinkedIn : https://www.linkedin.com/in/osman-

bolat-b9ba078a/

EDUCATION

Hacettepe University (2018-2024)

Industrial Engineering (English)

Gazi University 2016-2017)

Otomotiv Technology - associate degree

Grade: 2.81/4

Hava Astsubay MYO (2015-2016)

 Adana Sunar Nuri Çomu Anadolu High School (2011-2015)

LANGUAGE

English: Reading: B2, Writing: B2, Speaking: B2

COMPOTENCIES

Solidworks : 3/5
 CANIAS : 3/5
 Word :4/5
 Excel :4/5
 Powerpoint :4/5

CERTIFICATE

<u>CNC Certificate (Gazi University BELTEK course)</u>
 To have the competence to operate and use machining machines and to process machine parts.

REFERENCES

Bekir SAĞLAMYÜREK
 DORA Makina Kurucu Ortağı
 0 552 676 8500

• <u>İbrahim YARSAN</u> OSSA Yönetim Kurulu Başkanı 0 552 415 5775